<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.Kontact.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kontact</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKontactxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Kontact</name>
  <description>
    <p>
      Kontact is the integrated solution to your personal information management (PIM) needs.
      It combines well-known KDE applications like KMail, KOrganizer and KAddressBook into a single interface to provide easy access to mail,
      scheduling, address book and other PIM functionality.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Kontact és la solució integral per a la gestió de la vostra informació personal (PIM) que necessiteu. Combina aplicacions KDE conegudes com el KMail, KOrganizer i KAddressBook en una única interfície per a facilitar l'accés al correu, la planificació, la llibreta d'adreces i altres funcionalitats del PIM.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Kontact ist das integrierte Programm für Persönliches Informationsmanagement (PIM). Es kombiniert bekannte KDE-Programme wie KMail, KOrganizer und KAddressBook unter einer einheitlichen Oberfläche. Damit hat man einfachen Zugriff auf E-Mail, Termine, Adressbuch und weitere PIM-Funktionen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Ο Kontact είναι η ενσωματωμένη λύση για τις ανάγκες διαχείρισης των προσωπικών σας πληροφοριών (PIM). Συνδυάζει γνωστές εφαρμογές του KDE όπως τα KMail, KOrganizer και KAddressBook σε μια και μόνο γραφική διεπαφή για να παρέχει εύκολη πρόσβαση σε ηλ. αλληλογραφία, προγραμματισμό, βιβλίο διευθύνσεων και άλλες λειτουργικότητες PIM.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Kontact is the integrated solution to your personal information management (PIM) needs. It combines well-known KDE applications like KMail, KOrganizer and KAddressBook into a single interface to provide easy access to mail, scheduling, address book and other PIM functionality.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Kontact es la solución integrada para sus necesidades de gestión de información personal (PIM). Combina aplicaciones conocidas de KDE como KMail, KOrganizer y KAddressBook en una interfaz sencilla para proporcionar acceso a correo, planificación, libretas de direcciones y otras funcionalidades de PIM.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kontact on integroitu ratkaisu henkilökohtaisen tiedonhallintasi (PIM) tarpeisiin. Se yhdistää tunnetut KDE-sovellukset kuten KMailin, KOrganizerin ja KAddressBookin yhteen käyttöliittymään, jolloin voit helposti käyttää sähköpostia, ajastuksia, osoitekirjaa tai muita PIM-toimintoja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Kontact az integrált megoldás az Ön személyi információkezelési igényeire. Egy felületen kombinálja a jól ismert KDE alkalmazásokat, mint például a KMail, KOrganizer és KAddressBook, hogy egyszerűen hozzáférhessen leveleihez, naptáraihoz, címjegyzékeihez és más szolgáltatásokhoz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Kontact는 통합된 개인 정보 관리(PIM) 도구입니다. KMail, KOrganizer, KAddresssBook 등 KDE 프로그램을 한 자리에서 접근할 수 있으며, 이메일, 일정, 주소록 및 기타 PIM 기능에 접근할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Kontact er en integrert løsning på dine problemer men å håndtere personlig informasjon (PIM). Den kobler sammen velkjente KDE-programmer som KMail, KOrganizer og KAddressBook til en felles brukerflate som gir enkel tilgang til e-post, tidsplanlegging, adressebok og andre PIM-funksjoner.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Kontact is de inbuut Lösen för Dien Persöönlich-Informatschonen-Pleeg (PIM). Dat föhrt faken bruukt KDE-Programmen as KMail, KOrganizer un KAdressbook binnen een Böversiet tosamen; so is de Togriep op Nettpost, Planen, Adressbook un anner PIM-Funkschonen bannig eenfach.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kontact is een alles-in-één oplossing voor het beheren van al uw persoonlijke behoeften van beheer (PIM). Het combineert welbekende KDE-toepassingen als KMail, KOrganizer en KAddressbook tot één geheel, zodat u snel en eenvoudig toegang hebt tot uw e-mail, agenda, adressen en andere handige PIM-toepassingen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Kontact jest zintegrowanym rozwiązaniem odpowiadającym na potrzeby zarządzania informacjami osobistymi (ZIO). Łączy znane aplikacje KDE takie jak KMail, KOrganizer oraz Książka adresowa w program o jednym układzie sterowania, aby umożliwić łatwy dostęp do poczty, planowania, książki adresowej i innych funkcjonalności ZIO.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Kontact é a solução integrada para as suas necessidades de gestão de informações pessoais (PIM). Combina as conhecidas aplicações do KDE que são o  KMail, o KOrganizer e o KAddressBook numa única interface, de forma a dar um acesso simples ao correio, calendários, livros de endereço e outras funcionalidades de PIM.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Kontact é a solução integrada para suas necessidades de gerenciamento de informações pessoais (PIM). Ele agrupa os aplicativos conhecidos do KDE, como o KMail, o KOrganizer e o KAddressBook em uma única interface, para oferecer um acesso simples ao e-mail, à agenda, ao livro de endereços e a outras funcionalidades de PIM.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Kontact je integrované riešenie pre vaše potreby správy osobných informácií (PIM). Kombinuje dobre známe KDE aplikácie ako KMail, KOrganizer a KAddressBook do jedného rozhrania na poskytnutie ľahkému prístupu k pošte, plánovaniu, adresáru a iným funkciám PIM.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Kontact je enovit paket za upravljanje osebnih podatkov (PIM). V enovit vmesnik združuje znane programe za KDE kot npr. KMail, KOrganizer in KAddressBook in ponuja enostaven dostop do e-pošte, razporejanja opravil, imenika in drugih funkcij.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kontact är den integrerade lösningen för personlig informationshantering (PIM). Den kombinerar välkända KDE-program såsom Kmail, Korganizer och adressboken i ett enda gränssnitt för att enkelt ge tillgång till e-post, schemaläggning, adresser och annan funktionalitet för personlig informationshantering.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kontact — інтегроване рішення для забезпечення ваших потреб у керуванні особистими даними (PIM). Ця програма поєднує добре відомі програми KDE, зокрема KMail, KOrganizer та KAddressBook у межах єдиного інтерфейсу, який полегшує доступ до пошти, планів, адресної книги та інших можливостей з керування особистими даними.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKontact is the integrated solution to your personal information management (PIM) needs. It combines well-known KDE applications like KMail, KOrganizer and KAddressBook into a single interface to provide easy access to mail, scheduling, address book and other PIM functionality.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.kontact.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kontact</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdepim/kontact/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kontact.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kontact</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
